

### CONTACT



23 Waterfall Road, Paraparaumu

◩

cameron.soulsby@gmail.com



+64 27 632 6244

### **KEY STRENGTHS**

### Leadership

Proven record in successfully leading and supporting a large team in a challenging alpine environment

### Communication

Confident communicating in a diplomatic and open-minded manner in high pressure situations

### **Customer Service**

Focused on delivering a world-class experience to guests at each step of their product journey

### Safety

A strong emphasis on Health and Safety as an integral part of everyday operations

Decisive and confident in managing emergency situations

## **Organization & Planning**

A reputation for reliability and results, driven by disciplined personal organization habits and ownership of projects from beginning to end

### **Problem Solving**

Ability to discover novel solutions to problems through fostering genuine curiosity in a diverse range of viewpoints and by reasoning from first principles

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Software & IT (Honours, First Class)

Graduate Diploma in Software & IT

Bachelor of Commerce & Management (Economics)

# **CAM SOULSBY**

## PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

After 7 years of experience leading operational teams in the alpine resort industry, and a more recent role leading operations in a FinTech start-up, I am looking for an opportunity to step into a leadership role that will provide a new professional challenge and an exciting lifestyle.

I can deliver value to an organization through the development of high-performing teams, strong company culture, and robust processes and systems to drive operational efficiency.

My strengths in organization and project management allow me to keep on top of a diverse range of projects in a complex environment, while maintaining a reputation for reliability and delivery of consistent results.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

### **mStable**

Head of Operations

2021-2022

- Leading operations for a team of 15 building a Decentralised Finance application
- Handling day to day HR, payroll, accounting, and legal tasks for legal entities in Germany, Australia and New Zealand as well as for a Decentralized Autonomous Organization
- Navigating a complex legal and regulatory environment in an emerging space
- Working with a global and fully remote team and managing the resulting coordination challenges

### NZSki - Queenstown

Guest Services Head of Department

2020-2021

- Leading a team of frontline Guest Services staff as well as a Reservations team, responding to a demanding flow of incoming calls and emails
- Working closely with other NZSki teams to improve products and systems

## NZSki - The Remarkables Ski Area

Lift Operations Head of Department

2015-2019

- Managing a team of up to 45 Lift Operators and 3 Team Leaders
- Recruiting staff, organising and co-ordinating training, assessing qualifications, departmental planning, developing manuals and procedures, creating rosters, purchasing, performance reviews, attending operations meetings and working closely with other departments
- Overseeing daily operations to ensure exceptional customer service

Lift Operations Team Leader

2014

• Helping to lead a team of 35 Lift Operators

Lift Operator

2012-2013

Working as part of the Lift Operations team

### Niseko Village Ski Area, Hokkaido, Japan

Lift Operations Team Leader

2016-2017

Part of Niseko Village's first-ever group of native English-speaking Lift Operators

## **REFERENCES**

Ross Lawrence – Ski Area Manager at The Remarkables: (contact available on request)
Michel Lepage – former GMO at The Remarkables: (contact available on request)
Fiona Boyer – GM Customer, NZSki: (contact available on request)
James Simpson – Founder & CEO, mStable (contact available on request)